https://www.mlagb.com/terms-and-conditions/

Terms and ConditionsIn using this website you are deemed to have read and agreed to the following terms and conditions:TerminologyThe following terminology applies to these
Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all
Agreements:“User”, “You” and “Your” refers to you, the
person accessing this website and accepting the company’s terms and conditions.“The company”, “Ourselves”, “We” and “Us”,
refers to our organisation, The MLAGB.“Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both
the user and ourselves, or either the user or ourselves.All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and
consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance
to the user in the most appropriate manner, whether by formal meetings of a
fixed duration, or any other means, for the express purpose of meeting the
user's needs in respect of provision of the company’s stated services/products,
in accordance with and subject to, prevailing English Law.Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.Privacy StatementWe are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read our detailed privacy policy also available on our website.ConfidentialityUser records are regarded as confidential and
therefore will not be divulged to any unauthorised third party, unless if
legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.Users have the right to request sight of, and
copies of any and all user Records we keep with regards to themselves, on the
proviso that we are given reasonable notice of such a request.Users are requested to retain copies of any
literature issued in relation to the provision of our services.Where appropriate, we shall issue users with
appropriate written information, handouts or copies of records as part of an
agreed contract, for the benefit of both parties.We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information stored on this website to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.Disclaimer, Exclusions and LimitationsThe information on this website is provided on
an “as is” basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, this company:Excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its
contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other
third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the company’s literature; andExcludes all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of
business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable,
arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this company of
the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer,
computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other
direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.This company does not however exclude liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are affected.AvailabilityUnless otherwise stated, the services featured
on this website are only available within The United Kingdom (Great Britain and
Northern Ireland), or in relation to postings from the United Kingdom.All advertising is intended solely for the
United Kingdom market.You are solely responsible for evaluating the
fitness for a particular purpose of any downloads, programs and text available
through this site.Redistribution or republication of any part of
this site or its content is prohibited, including such by framing or other
similar or any other means, without the express written consent of the company.The company does not warrant that the service
from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is
provided to the best ability.By using this service you thereby indemnify
this company, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage,
in whatever manner, howsoever caused.Log FilesWe use IP addresses to analyse trends,
administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic
information for aggregate use.IP addresses are not linked to personally
identifiable information.Additionally, for systems administration,
detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers
automatically log standard access information including browser type, access
times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL.This information is not shared with third
parties and is used only within this company on a need-to-know basis.Any individually identifiable information
related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated
above without your explicit permission.CookiesLike most interactive web sites this company website
uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit.Cookies are used in some areas of our site to
enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people
visiting.Links to this websiteIf you create a link to a page of this website
you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above
will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.Links from this websiteWe do not monitor or review the content of
other party’s websites which are linked to from this website.Opinions expressed or material appearing on
such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be
regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material.Please be aware that we are not responsible
for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites.We encourage our users to be aware when they
leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites.You should evaluate the security and
trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through
this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them.This company will not accept any
responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting
from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.Copyright NoticeCopyright and other relevant intellectual
property rights exist on all text relating to the company’s services and the
full content of this website.Force MajeureNeither party shall be liable to the other for
any failure to perform any obligation under any Agreement which is due to an
event beyond the control of such party including but not limited to any Act of
God, terrorism, war, Political insurgence, insurrection, riot, civil unrest,
act of civil or military authority, uprising, earthquake, flood or any other
natural or man made eventuality outside of our control, which causes the
termination of an agreement or contract entered into, nor which could have been
reasonably foreseen.Any Party affected by such event shall
forthwith inform the other Party of the same and shall use all reasonable
endeavours to comply with the terms and conditions of any agreement contained
herein.WaiverFailure of either Party to insist upon strict
performance of any provision of this or any Agreement or the failure of either
Party to exercise any right or remedy to which it, he or they are entitled
hereunder shall not constitute a waiver thereof and shall not cause a diminution
of the obligations under this or any agreement.No waiver of any of the provisions of this or
any agreement shall be effective unless it is expressly stated to be such and
signed by both Parties.GeneralThe laws of England and Wales govern these
terms and conditions.By accessing this website you consent to these
terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts in
all disputes arising out of such access.If any of these terms are deemed invalid or
unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to the exclusions and
limitations set out above), then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be
severed from these terms and the remaining terms will continue to apply.Failure of the company to enforce any of the
provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any agreement, or failure
to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such
provisions and shall not affect the validity of these terms and conditions or
of any agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each
and every provision.These Terms and Conditions shall not be
amended, modified, varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly
authorised representatives of the company.Notification of ChangesThe company reserves the right to change these
conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site
will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms.If there are any changes to our privacy
policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and
on other key pages on our site.If there are any changes in how we use our
site users’ Personally Identifiable Information, notification by e-mail or
postal mail will be made to those affected by this change.Any changes to our privacy policy will be
posted on our web site – you are therefore advised to re-read this statement on
a regular basisThese terms and conditions form part of the
agreement between the user and ourselves. Your accessing of this website and/or
undertaking of a booking or agreement indicates your understanding, agreement
to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and Conditions
contained herein. Your statutory Consumer Rights are unaffected.
By using this website you agree to accept our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions Accept
